http://www.camarda.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Menu About UsAbout UsTeamHistoryRecognitionMissionCommunityAdvice401(k) Rollovers / ManagementChoosing AdvisorsInvestment ManagementWealth ManagementEstate PlanningTax ReductionAsset ProtectionRetirement PlanningBusiness Owner PlanningResourcesCareersDisclosure / PoliciesContact UsFleming IslandJacksonvillePonte VedraLet’s TalkCamarda Wealth Advisory Group (“Camarda”), maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to protect its clients’ nonpublic personal information (“information”). Through this policy and its underlying procedures, Camarda attempts to secure the confidentiality of customer records and information and protect against anticipated threats or hazards to the security or integrity of customer records and information.It is the policy of Camarda to restrict access to all current and former clients’ information (i.e., information and records pertaining to personal background, investment objectives, financial situation, tax information/returns, investment holdings, account numbers, account balances, etc.) to those employees and affiliated/nonaffiliated entities who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to the client. Camarda may disclose the client’s information if Camarda is: (1) previously authorized to disclose the information to individuals and/or entities not affiliated with Camarda, including, but not limited to the client’s other professional advisors and/or service providers (i.e., attorney, accountant, insurance agent, broker-dealer, investment adviser, account custodian, etc.); (2) required to do so by judicial or regulatory process; or (3) otherwise permitted to do so in accordance with the parameters of applicable federal and/or state privacy regulations. The disclosure of information contained in any document completed by the client for processing and/or transmittal by Camarda in order to facilitate the commencement/continuation/termination of a business relationship between the client and a nonaffiliated third party service provider (i.e., broker-dealer, investment adviser, account custodian, insurance company, etc.), including information contained in any document completed and/or executed by the client for Camarda (i.e., advisory agreement, client information form, etc.), shall be deemed as having been automatically authorized by the client with respect to the corresponding nonaffiliated third party service provider.Camarda permits only authorized employees and affiliates who have signed a copy of Camarda’s Privacy Policy to have access to client information. Employees violating Camarda’s Privacy Policy will be subject to Camarda’s disciplinary process. Additionally, whenever Camarda hires other organizations to provide services to Camarda’s clients, Camarda will require them to sign confidentiality agreements and/or the Privacy Policy.Should you have any questions regarding the above, please contact Kimberly Camarda at 888­CAMARDA (888-226-2732), ext. 203.AFFILIATE MARKETING INFORMATION & OPT OUTThis notice regarding affiliated marketing is provided by Camarda. You should know that Federal law gives you the right to limit some but not all marketing from our affiliates. Federal law also requires us to give you this notice to tell you about your options regarding the marketing efforts of our affiliates.Camarda is affiliated through common ownership and control with Camarda Consultants, LLC, a licensed insurance agency and business consulting firm providing business planning, estate planning, insurance and other non-advisory services to its clients (“Camarda Consultants”). You may limit Camarda Consultants from marketing these products or services to you based on personal information that we may collect or compile regarding you and your relationship with us and share with them. This information may include, among other relevant eligibility information, your income, your account history with us, insurance, estate planning or other needs revealed through financial planning, consulting or other advisory services and your credit score.Your choice to limit marketing offers from Camarda Consultants will remain in effect until you tell us that you would like to change your choice. If you have already made a choice to limit marketing offers from Camarda Consultants, you do not need to act again unless you would like to change that choice.To limit marketing offers, please contact Kimberly Camarda at 888-CAMARDA (888-226-2732), ext. 203.Office Locations:4371 US-17, Suite 201Fleming Island, FL 32003166 A1A North, Suite 101Ponte Vedra Beach, FL 320824600 Touchton Rd., Bldg. 100 Suite 150,Jacksonville, FL 32246Talk to an advisor: 800-262-1083Connect with us:
Linkedin
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
AboutInvestment ManagementWealth Management401(k) RolloversFleming IslandPonte Vedra BeachJacksonvilleLocations
MenuAboutInvestment ManagementWealth Management401(k) RolloversFleming IslandPonte Vedra BeachJacksonvilleLocations
Scroll back to top Talk with an advisor today!Send us your contact information and the best time to call, and we’ll contact you.
